"迷失"前情回顾...
Previously on "lost"...
他们来了 开始争斗
They come. They fight.
他们毁灭 最后腐烂
They destroy. They corrupt.
结局总是相同的
It always ends the same.
但是只结束一次
It only ends once.
在这之前所有的事情都是过程
Anything that happens before that is just progress.
我不会杀Jacob的 Ben
I'm not gonna kill Jacob, Ben.
你会
You are.
- 照我说的做 Ben - 我只想让你明白一件事情
- Do what I asked you to, Ben. - I want you to understand one thing.
你有机会选择的
You have a choice.
他们来了
They're coming.
在天鹅站工地的达摩组织的人们...
The Dharma folks at the swan worksite...
他们会在地上钻井
They're gonna drill into the ground
意外的钻入了一块巨大的隐藏能量中
And accidentally tap into a massive pocket of energy.
我觉得我能消除这股能量
I think I can negate that energy.
- 我会去引爆氢弹的 - 如果我们按照Faraday说的做 飞机就不会失事
- I'm gonna detonate a hydrogen bomb. - If we can do what Faraday said, plane never crashes.
815号航班会在洛杉矶降落
Flight 815 lands in los angeles.
快点 医生! 你在等什么?!
Hurry up, Doc! What are you waitin' for?!
我们钻到能量块了!
We hit the pocket!
Juliet啊
Juliet!
- 我抓住你了 不 不要松手! - 啊!
- I got you. No, don't let go! - Aah!
Juliet啊
Juliet!
不!
No!
不! 不 快点!
No! No, come on!
快点!
Come on!
快点 你这混蛋!
Come on, you son of a bitch!
饮料还满意么?
So how's the drink?
呃...
Uh...
还不错
It's good.
这个反应可不够强烈啊
That's not a very strong reaction.
好吧 这个... 也不是个烈性饮料
Well, it's... it's not a very strong drink.
- 谁也别告诉 - 这是我们的秘密
- Don't tell anyone. - It'll be our secret.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
机长已将"系好安全带"指示打开
The captain has turned on the "fasten seat belts" sign.
- 系好你们的安全带 - 这是正常情况
- And keep your seat belts fastened. - It's normal.
我丈夫说了 这飞机想呆在天上
My husband said the planes want to stay in the air.
听起来像个聪明人
Sounds like a smart man.
绝对是的
You be sure and tell him that
你可以等他从厕所回来把这句话告诉他
when he gets back from the bathroom.
好啊 他不在的时候 我会陪着你的
Well, I'll keep you company until he does.
别担心
Don't worry.
你可以放开了
You can let go now.
没事了 你... 你可以放手了
It's okay. You...you can let go.
- 看来我们成功了 - 是啊 我们当然成功了
- Looks like we made it. - Yeah. We sure did.
很抱歉出现了突然的撞击 大伙
Sorry about the unexpected bumps, folks.
我们刚刚遇到一块扰动气流
We just hit a pocket of rough air.
之后的旅途会很平稳
It should be a smooth ride from here on out.
下次提醒我要憋着 好么?
Remind me to hold it next time, will ya?
我在厕所差点死过去
I almost died in that bathroom.
我终于知道衣服在被烘干的时候是什么感觉了
Now I know how the laundry feels when it's in the dryer.
我想你了
I missed you.
我也想你了 美女
I missed you, too, beautiful.
- 对不起 - 哦 对不起 伙计 这是你的座位?
- Excuse me. - Oh, I'm sorry, mate. Is this your seat?
- 乘务员说是空的 - 不 不 我是坐在窗边的
- The stewardess said it was empty. - No. No, I'm at the window.
哦 好的
Oh, right.
那么 伙计 你介意我坐这儿么?
Listen, mate, do you mind if I sit here?
就是我边上的那个小伙子一直在打鼾
It's just the fella next to me has been snoring
- 我们从悉尼起飞之后就开始了 - 好的 没问题
Ever since we took off from sydney. Yeah, no problem.
谢了 兄弟
Thanks, brother.
怎么了?
Something wrong?
不 没事 只是你...
No. No, you just...
我是不是认识你呢?
Do I know you from somewhere?
啊 我也不确定
Well, I'm not sure.
我叫Desmond
Desmond.
嗯Jack
Jack.
很高兴见到你 Jack...
Nice to meet you, Jack...
或者说再次见到你
Or to see you again.
啊! 不! 不! Juliet!
Aah! No! No! Juliet!
- 我抓住你了 不 别放手! - 啊!
- I got you. No, don't let go! - Aah!
Juliet! 不!
Juliet! No!
快点 你这混蛋!
Come on, you son of a bitch!
喂?
Hello?
喂?!
Hello?!
嘿!
Hey!
嘿! 嘿! Kate!
Hey! Hey! Kate!
好了好了 是我 Miles. 没事了
It's okay. It's me, Miles. It's okay.
- 发生了什么? - 什么?
- What happened? - What?
我们在哪?
Where are we?
我听不到... 你在说什么 你的耳朵有没有嗡嗡响?
I can't... I can't here you. Are your ears ringing?
这是什么?
What is it?
我们又回来了
We're back.
回哪去了?
Back where?
不
No.
这不是工地么?
Is that the construction site?
不
No.
那是天鹅舱...
That's the swan hatch...
Desmond炸过之后的
After Desmond blew it up.
我猜我们没在1977年 哈?
Guess we're not in 1977, huh?
是Jack? Jack
Jack? Jack.
你能听见我说话么? Jack!
Can you hear me? Jack!
发生了什么?
What happened?
- 我们在那? - 在舱门边上
- Where are we? - At the hatch.
什么? 他们还是造了这个?
What? They built it?
对 他们造了
Yeah. They built it.
住手Sawyer!
Sawyer!
呃!
Uhh!
你错了!
You were wrong!
那是该死的天鹅站舱口...
That's the damn swan hatch...
爆炸过后就像是我们留下来的一样
Blown up just like we left it
在我们开始穿越时空之前!
Before we started jumping through time!
你说过我们甚至可以阻止它建立!
You said we could stop it from ever gettin' built!
- 我们的飞机也不会坠落到这个岛! - 别这样了!
- That our plane would never crash on this island! - Stop it!
- 这儿不是洛杉矶! - 别这样了!
- This ain't l.a.x.! - Stop it!
你让我们白折腾了!
You blew us right back where we started!
而Juliet却死了
Except Juliet's dead.
她死了 你个狗娘养的 都是你的错
She's dead, you son of a bitch, 'cause you were wrong.
Sawyer啊...
Sawyer...
对不起
I'm sorry.
我还以为我们会...
I thought we were supposed to...
本以为会起作用的
I thought it would work.
可它没有!
Well, it didn't!
你在排队?
You in line?
不 在等我的朋友
No, I'm just waiting for my friend.
- 哦! - 喔
- Oh! - Whoa.
- 对不起 我没有... - 没关系
- I'm sorry. I didn't... - It's okay.
- 我没看到你在这儿 - 没关系
- I didn't see you there. - It's okay.
我们坐回去吧 亲爱的
Let's get back to our seats, sweetheart.
嗯
Mmm.
千层面
Lasagna.
别 别用刀叉 亲爱的
No. No knife and fork for you, honey.
你觉得我会干嘛
What do you think I'm gonna do,&
捅了你然后逃跑?
Stab you and run?
嘿 走路看着点 伙计
Hey, watch we're you're going, buddy.
对不起 我的错
Sorry. My bad.
说吧 好吗? 就一遍
Say it. Come on, please? Just once.
- 我真不想这么干 兄弟 - 我爱死那广告了
- I really don't want to, dude. - I love those commercials.
说吧 用澳洲口音说
Come on. Just do the Australian accent,
我就不来烦你了
And I'll leave you alone.
好吧 好吧 好吧
All right. Fine. All right.
哦!开始咕咕咯咯的一天吧 伙计!
Oi! Have a cluckity-cluck day, mate!
你知道这是谁吗?
You know who this is?
这是... 是咯咯叫先生鸡肉店的老板
This is...this is the owner of Mr. Cluck's chicken.
而他... 他现在正和我们一起
And he's...and he's back here riding coach
- 坐在飞机上! 对吧? - 那又怎么了?
- With the rest of us yutzes! Huh? - How about th?
嘿 嗯 我能问下
Hey, um, do you mind me asking,
像你这样的人是如何有了这么大的一家公司的呢?
How exactly did a guy like you get to own a major corporation?
我中了彩票又喜欢吃鸡
I won the lottery and I like chicken,
就把它买下喽
So I bought it.
噢 真好
Oh. Good.
你真行
Good for you.
你知道吗 你真不该告诉其他人你中奖了
You know, you really shouldn't tell people you won the lottery.
是吗? 为什么?
Yeah? Why not?
因为他们会利用你 这就是原因
Cause they'll take advantage of you. That's why not.
谢谢你的忠告 兄弟 但这不会发生的
Thanks for the advice, dude, but it's not gonna happen.
不会 是吗?
It's not, huh?
是的 我运气向来很好
Nope. Nothing bad ever happens to me.
我是世界上最幸运的人
I'm the luckiest guy alive.
刚刚怎么了?
What just happened?
我看到了一阵闪光
I found a flashlight.
兄弟 谁在乎啊? 白昼瞬间成黑夜了
Dude, who cares? The sky just went from day to night.
- 怎么回事啊?! - 我猜我们是穿越时空了
- What happened?! - I think we moved through time.
你怎么知道?
How do you know that?
白色闪光 头痛 听不见声音
White flash. Headache. Can't hear.
- 我以前也发生过 - Jack和其他人呢?
- Happened to me before. - What about Jack and everyone else?
- 他们也穿越时空了吗? - 我不知道
- Did they move through time, too? - I don't know.
他们开了另外一辆货车去工地了
They took one of the other vans and went up to the worksite.
接着我就听到了枪声...
And then I heard gunfire...
- 嘘! - 你说过我们的飞机再也不会坠到这个岛上的!
- Shh! - You said that our plane would never crash on this island!
- 听到了吗 兄弟? 是Sawyer - 呆这儿陪着Sayid
- You hear that, dude? It's Sawyer. - Stay here with Sayid.
炸弹肯定爆炸了
The bomb must've gone off.
你觉得原子弹爆炸了以后我们还能站在这儿?
You think an atom bomb went off, we'd still be standing here?!
我不懂
I don't know.
没错! 你不懂! 你终于承认不懂了!
That's right! You don't! For once, you don't know!
Jack啊!
Jack!
Sayid需要帮助
Sayid needs help.
- 他在哪儿? - 在货车那儿 Hurley陪着他
- Where is he? - With Hurley at the van.
- 两分钟路程 - 救命
- Two minutes away. - Help.
他还在流血 我们不知道该怎么办
He's still bleeding. We don't know what to do.
救命
Help me.
怎么说啊 医生?
So what do you say, doc?
又想到一个好主意来救Sayid了?
Got another great idea to save Sayid?
- 没准周围又埋了一颗核弹 - 嘿 闭嘴!
- Maybe there's a nuke laying around. - Hey, shut up!
救命
Help.
Juliet啊
Juliet!
James吗?
James?
噢 天呐
Oh, my god.
Juliet啊!
Juliet!
哦 天呐 哦 天呐 恶心死了
Oh, god. Oh, god, this is gross.
别担心 兄弟
Don't worry, dude.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be fine.
我死后...
When I die...
你觉得我会发生什么?
What do you think will happen to me?
别... 别说话了 哥们
Just... just try not to talk, dude.
我虐待过多少人自己都记不清了
I've tortured more people than I can remember.
我杀人
I murdered.
不管我去哪儿...
Wherever I'm going...
都不会是好地方
It can't be very pleasant.
- Sayid 行了 - 我活该
- Sayid, come on. - I deserve it.
谁?
Hello?
Jin吗?
Jin?
Jin啊
Jin!
我有枪的!
I've got a gun!
我也知道怎么用!
And I know how to shoot it!
你好 Hugo
Hello, Hugo.
有时间吗?
You got a minute?
你盯着他们干吗?
他们看起来挺开心的
把衣服扣上
你在浪费时间 伙计
You're wasting your time, man.
这架飞机要是在大海中间坠落的话
This plane goes down in the ocean way out here,
我想我们的生存几率绝对为零
I think our chances of survival are exactly zero.
实际上 平静的海面再加一个好的飞行员
Actually, in calm seas w-with a good pilot,
我们可以在水面迫降的
We could survive a water landing.
还有 嗯 燃料罐浮力很大的
And, uh, the fuel tanks are buoyant enough
完全可以支持到我们上救生筏
To keep us afloat until we got in the life rafts.
怎么了?
What?
没什么 你知道的可真不少
No, it's just impressive you know that.
你在澳大利亚干吗了?
What were you doing in Australia?
生意还是度假?
Business or pleasure?
度假 你呢?
Pleasure. You?
我去处理一下和我妹妹糟糕的关系
I went down to get my sister out of a bad relationship
结果是她不买我的帐
That it turns out she didn't want to get out of.
如此...
So...
我就在这儿了
Here I am.
那么说 你是来澳洲度假的了?
So what, you were just down under for vacation?
实际上 我是来徒步旅行的
Actually, I went on a walkabout.
是吗?
Really?
就像... 像鳄鱼邓迪似的?
Like... like Crocodile Cundee?&
不 不太像
No, not exactly.
但... 但是 嗯 相当激烈了
But... but, uh, it was pretty intense.
我们... 我们在内陆呆了10天
We... we spent ten days in the outback
嗯 除了包和刀什么都不带
And, uh, nothing but our packs and our knives.
我们燃起篝火 在星空下入睡
We slept under the stars and made our own fires,
自己打猎
Hunted our own food.
哇
Wow.
我要是两天不带电话就活不了
I wouldn't make it two days without my cell phone.
你不是在跟我开玩笑吧 对吗?
You're not pulling my leg, are ya?
我为什么要跟你开玩笑呢?
Why would I pull your leg?
我的事完了之后 就跟你混一阵
This thing goes down, I'm sticking with you.
你不用盯着火看了
You can stop staring at the fire.
Jacob死了
Jacob's gone.
他死了
He's gone.
他为什么不还手?
Why didn't he fight back?
他为什么让我杀他?
Why did he let me just kill him?
我想是他知道他已经被打败了
I guess he knew that he was beaten.
Ben啊...
Ben...
我要你出去
I want you to go outside
告诉Richard 我想跟他谈谈
And tell Richard that I need to talk to him.
跟他谈... 什么?
Talk to him about... What?
那是我和Richard的事
That's between me and Richard.
- 没有别的原因 - 不 事情不应该那样的
- There's no other reason. - No, that's not how it's gonna be.
- 你应该... - 你不能进去
- You have to... - you're not going in there.
听我说 我已经决定了 现在我要你...
Listen to me. I already did. Now I'm asking you to...
到那边去...
Body over by the...
只要退回去一点 好吗?
Just back up a little. Okay?
他们是谁?
Who are they?
除了那些
Other than the fact
和我们一起在Ajira航班上的人
that I know they were on the Ajira flight with us,
我所知道的就是 他们打晕了我
All I know is they knocked me out
把我关进了某个小屋
And dragged my ass to some cabin,
他们很快又把屋子给烧了 然后
Which they promptly burned, then...
把我和棺材里那个死人又带到了这里
Brought me here along with the dead guy in the box.
他们说他们是好人
They say they're the good guys.
我也不信
I'm not buying it either.
听我说 嘿! 听我说 给我仔细听着
Listen to me. Hey! Listen to me, and listen carefully.
除非Jacob邀请 否则谁也不能进去
No one goes in there unless Jacob invites them in.
Richard 我们之所以来这里 就是因为Jacob邀请了我们
Richard, that's why we're here, because Jacob invited us.
问我那该死的雕像下边有什么
Asking me what's in the shadow of the damn statue
- 并不代表你是头儿 - 那谁是呢?
- Doesn't mean you're in charge. - Then who is?
Richard啊
Richard.
嘿 Ben
Ben.
里面怎么了?
What happened in there?
一切都好
Everything's fine.
John想跟你谈谈
John wants to speak to you.
- Jacob还好吧? - 不好意思 你哪位?
- Is Jacob all right? - I'm sorry. Who are you?
- 回答她的问题 Ben - 哦 那当然 Jacob很好
- Answer her question, Ben. - Well, of course Jacob's all right.
他们两个都在里面 John想跟你谈谈
They're both together inside. John just wants to talk to you.
- John想跟我谈谈? - 是的
- John wants to talk to me? - That's right.
Richard 你干什么? 我不明白
Richard, what are you doing? I don't understand.
哦 跟John谈话我很高兴
Well, I'm happy to talk to John.
但在我跟他谈之前 你最好先跟他谈谈
But before I do, maybe you should talk to him first.
坚持住 Juliet! 我们马上到!
Hang on, Juliet! We're coming!
呃!
Uhh!
Jin 手电筒
Jin. Flashlight.
把这根柱子移开 我就能下去了
We can move this beam. Think I can get down there.
唉! 这太重了 得拿点东西把这个拉起来 Jin!
Uhh! Too heavy. We need something to pull it. Jin!
货车! 里面有条链子 拿过来!
The van! There's chains in it. Go get 'em!
老兄 你在干啥?
Where you going, dude?
你跑这儿干啥?
And what are you doing here?
我在计程车里见过你
I mean, I meet you in a taxi,
你知道我的一切
and you know everything about me,
你还给了我一张
and you give me a plane ticket,
刚好能把我送回岛上的机票
which just so happens to get me back on this island.
你怎么知道将要发生的事?
How'd you know that was gonna happen?
听得到吗?
Hello?
能听得到吗? 为什么不回答我的问题?
Can you hear me? Why aren't you answering my questions?
我朋友Jin随时都可能回来
Look, my friend Jin's gonna be here any second,
- 你最好不要再忽略我了... - 你朋友Jin见不到我了
- So you better stop ignoring me... - Your friend Jin won't be able to see me.
为啥?
Why not?
因为我一小时前就死了
Because I died an hour ago.
抱歉 老兄 不好受吧
Sorry, dude. That sucks.
谢谢
Thanks.
怎么死的?
How'd you die?
被一个已经厌倦了我陪伴的老朋友杀的
I was killed by an old friend who grew tired of my company.
你又想让我做什么疯狂的事了 是吧?
You want me to do something crazy again, don't you?
不 Hugo 我要你救活Sayid
No. I need you to save Sayid, Hugo.
- 所以Jin去找Jack 让他... - Jin帮不了的
- Well, that's why Jin went to go get Jack, to... - Jin can't help him.
你要把Sayid带到庙里
You need to take Sayid to the temple.
这是他活命的唯一机会
That's the only chance he's got.
其他的人在那也会安全的
And the rest of them will be safe there.
庙? 我应该知道那是什么吧?
The temple? I'm supposed to know what that is?
Jin知道
Jin knows.
让他带你去有洞的那堵墙
Tell him to take you to the hole in the wall
他和法国人曾去过那里
where he was with the French team.
经过那个入口 你们就能到庙里去了
Through that opening, you can get into the temple.
你还拿着我给你的吉他盒吧?
You still have that guitar case I gave you?
对
Yeah.
带上它
Bring it.
老兄 你是谁?
Who are you, dude?
我是Jacob
I'm Jacob.
Hurley啊!
Hurley!
帮我抬一下Sayid
Help me with Sayid.
我们得把他放到车里面 Juliet需要帮忙
We have to get him into the van. Juliet needs our help.
快! 该走了!
Come on! We have to go!
Jin 如果我让你
Jin, if I asked you
带我去那个带洞的墙那里
to take me to where there's like a hole in the wall,
就是你当初和法国人去过的地方
where you went with the french team,
你知道我在说什么吗?
would you know what I was talking about?
知道
Yes.
很好
Good.
我去拿链子
I'll get the chain.
Juliet呢?
Juliet?
冷静 Sawyer 冷静
Stop it. Stop, Sawyer.
车已经到了 链子马上就来了
The van is here. The chains are comin'.
- 她已经不出声了 - 她知道我们在这儿 她应该在休息
- She ain't makin' any more noises. - She knows we're here. She's probably just resting.
Juliet啊!
Juliet!
如果她死了 我一定会杀了他
If she dies, I'll kill him.
女士们先生们 没有任何紧急情况
Ladies and gentlemen, nothing to be alarmed about,
如果您是医生
but if there is a doctor on board,
请按下您的呼叫按钮
would you please press your call button?
- 先生 您是医生? - 是
- Sir, you're a doctor? - Yes.
您能不能跟我来呢? 非常感谢您的帮助
Could you come with me, please? We appreciate your help.
一位乘客半小时前 进了洗手间
A passenger went into the restroom about half an hour ago,
但我们敲门却没人答应
and he's not responding when we knock.
- 这位先生是医生 如果他昏迷了的话... - 我... 我觉得他把锁弄坏了
- This man's a doctor. If he's unconscious in there... - I... I think he tampered with the lock.
锁... 锁好像被堵住了 我也不清楚
It's... it's jammed or something. I don't know.
我能帮忙吗? 让一下
Can I be of assistance? Excuse me.
他没有呼吸了
He's not breathing.
后面怎么了 Earhart?
What's goin' on back there, Earhart?
- 一切平安 先生 请做好 - 好吧 看上去也正常着呢
- Yeah, everything's fine, sir. Please just stay in your seat. - Yeah. Looks peachy.
- 先生 我需要你帮忙 - 我能做什么?
- Sir, I'm gonna need your help. - What can I do?
我需要你...
I need you...
把这个按在他的口鼻上
Hold this over his nose and mouth.
- 按住 不要让空气跑出来了 - 好的 现在吗?
- Hold it there, and do not let any air escape. - Okay. Now?
是的 现在
Yes, now.
有什么东西卡在气管上了
Something's blocking his air passage.
必须打通
We have to open it up.
我需要 呃 尖锐的东西... 刮胡刀那样的
I need, uh, something sharp... a razor.
- 我有支笔 - 笔?
- I got a pen. - A pen?
- 有规定 飞机上不能带尖锐的东西 - 笔! 一支笔就够了
- It's regulation. There's nothing sharp. - A pen! Just a pen.
本来我的外套有支笔的 但是不见了
I had a pen in my jacket but it's gone.
该死
Damn it.
拿到了 拿到了
I got it. I got it.
放松 放轻松 呼吸
Relax. Just relax. Breathe.
我还活着?
I'm alive?
对 你还活着
Yeah. Ah, you're alive.
真可怕
Terrific.
- 好了? - 好了 Jin! 我们下面弄好了!
- Got it? - Okay, Jin! We're good down here!
拉!
Hit it!
给我手电筒
Give me the flashlight.
Juliet啊
Juliet.
好了
Ok.
Juliet 来我这 好了
Juliet. Come here. Okay.
Juliet啊?
Juliet?
Juliet 嘿 是我 醒醒 宝贝
Juliet, hey. I'm here. Come on, baby.
嘿 拜托 醒醒
Hey, come on, wake up.
醒醒
Wake up.
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
没事了
Okay.
我们... 我们... 这是在哪儿?
Where... Where... Where are we?
别担心了 你没事了
Don't worry about that. You're fine.
我要带你出去 听到了吗?
I gotta get you out of here, okay?
没有起作用
It didn't work.
我们还在岛上
We're still on the island.
没关系 没关系
It's okay. It's okay.
我只要把那个弄松一点你就可以出来了 听到了吗?
I just gotta get this loose enough to get you out, okay?
- 我要带你... - 不 我启动的炸弹 你还是在这儿
- I need to get you... - No, I hit the bomb. You're still here.
你做了什么?
You what?
你启动的炸弹?
You hit the bomb?
为什么?
Why?
我想你回家
I wanted you to be able to go home.
我想你回去
I wanted to make it
你就可以再也不回这该死的岛上了
so that you never came to this damn isld.
可是没起作用
And it didn't work.
嘘
Shh.
不要担心了
Don't you worry about that.
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
我要带你出去
I'm gonna get you outta here,
- 我们就可以一起回家了 你听到了吗? - Sawyer?
- and we're all gonna go home together. You hear me? - Sawyer?
就算我把子弹取出来 他还是会流血不止
Even if I could get the bullet out, the bleeding won't stop.
我实在无能无力了
There's nothing I can do for him.
我有办法
There's something I can do.
有一座庙
There's a temple.
我们把Sayid带到那里去 我们就能救他
If we can get Sayid there, we can save him.
- 你是怎么知道的? - 我们来这之前一个叫Jacob家伙告诉我的
- And you know this how? - This guy Jacob told me just before we got here.
Jacob是谁?
Who's Jacob?
有什么关系吗? 你能治好Sayid吗 Jack?
Does it matter? Can you fix Sayid, Jack?
不能
No.
那你让我来
Then you're gonna have to let me do it.
Ben 跟我说怎么回事
Ben, you need to talk to me.
你... 不跟我说那里到底发生了什么 他们就会不停的问我
I... I can't stop them unless you tell me what happened in there,
Jacob出什么事了
What happened to Jacob.
我们两个认识30年了 Ben
You and I have known each other for 30 years, Ben.
我以朋友的身份 来问你这个问题
I'm asking you this as a friend.
你想知道发生什么事了吗 Richard?
You wanna know what happened, Richard?
为什么你不自己进去看看呢?
Why don't you go inside and find out?
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我们要进去 他和我们一起进去
We're goin' in, and he's comin' with us.
Richard呢?
Where's Richard?
他没来
He's not coming.
那你身后是谁?
Then who is that behind you?
Jacob去哪儿了?
Where's Jacob?
Jacob死了
Jacob is dead.
你是谁?
Who are you?
别管我是谁
Don't worry about me.
我们来谈谈你
Let's talk about you.
我猜你是... 什么 Jacob的保镖
I'm assuming that you are... What, Jacob's bodyguards,
你一路上跟随到这个岛上来保护他?
and that you came all the way to this island to protect him?
好吧 我这有好消息
Well, I have good news.
Jacob就是在那儿的火灾中烧死的
Jacob burned up right there in that fire.
因此你什么也不用保护了 你可以走了
Therefore there's nothing left for you to protect. You can go.
你自由了
You're free.
杀了他!
Kill him!
分散开! 抓住他!
Spread out! Get him!
他去哪儿了?!
Where is he?!
抱歉让你看到我这样
I'm sorry yod to see me like that.
Sawyer啊?
Sawyer?
她还好吗?
Is she okay?
我正在努力呢!
I'm workin' on it!
啊!
Aah!
快点
Come on.
嗯! 好了
Uhh! Okay.
好了 我来救你了
Okay, I got you.
我在这 没事了
I got you. Okay.
好了 我在这 没事了
It's okay. I got you. Okay.
别担心
Don't worry.
我们应该找个时间去喝点咖啡
We should get coffee some time.
我会把你从这弄出来的
I gotta get you out of here.
我们可以AA制
We can go dutch.
嘿 Juliet?
Juliet?
是我
It's me.
嘿 James
James.
吻我
Kiss me.
没问题 金发美女
You got it, Blondie.
我必须告诉你一些事
I have to tell you something.
非常 非常重要
It's really, really important.
你告诉我
You tell me.
告诉我
Tell me.
嘿 Julie?
Julie?
呃... 你告诉我
Ba... you tell me
哦 天哪
Oh, god.
我在这
I'm here.
我... 我...
I'm... I'm...
都是你干的
You did this.
你不该就我的 伙计
You should've let that happen, man.
我本应该死了的
I was supposed to die.
别放在心上
Don't take it personally.
有些人就是连谢谢都不会说
Some people just don't know how to say thanks.
请问 你知道坐在我旁边的那个人
Excuse me, do you know what happened
- 去哪了吗? - 哦 我们刚才睡着了
- to the guy that was sitting next to me? - Oh, we were asleep.
女士们 先生们 我是Norr机长
Ladies and gentlemen, Captain Norr is here.
我们现在进入降落洛杉矶国际机场的最后阶段
We're now beginng our final descent into Los Angeles international airport.
我很高兴地告诉大家 洛杉矶今天天气很不错
I'm happy to tell you it's a beautiful day in Los Angeles.
72度 能见度6英里
72 degrees, 6 miles visibility
西南风每小时5英里
and winds out of the southwest at 5 miles an hour.
系好安全带 我们马上就到家了
Buckle up. We're almost home.
我现在要打开"系好安全带"提示了
I'll be putting on The "fasten seat belt" sign now.
我们会在几分钟后着陆
We'll be on the ground in just a few minutes.
非常感谢您乘坐大洋航空
Thank you so much for flying oceanic air.
我们路上要唱"昆巴亚"吗?
We gonna sing "kumbaya" on the way?
里面不是吉他 伙计
It's not a guitar, man.
那是什么?
Then what is it?
你跟他们一起吗?
You going with them?
不 我要去葬她
No, I'm gonna bury her.
我来帮你
Let me help you.
去帮Sayid吧
Help Sayid.
嘿 Miles 你介意来帮忙吗?
Hey, Miles. You mind hangin' back?
来了 老大
You got it, boss.
我会沿路留下记号 你就可以跟来了
I'll make sure to leave a trace so you can follow us.
我不会跟去的 Kate
I ain't followin' nobody, Kate.
- 准备好了吗? - 随时都可以
- You guys ready? - Whenever you are.
大洋公司的乘客
Oceanic passenger
Jack Shephard先生
Jack Shephard.
Jack Shephard 请立即去最近的服务台
Jack Shephard, please go to the nearest courtesy desk.
所有抵达的乘客们 请注意...
Attention all arriving passengers...
嗨 呃...
Hi. Uh...
我就是Jack Shephard 广播里叫我来的
I'm Jack Shephard. I was just paged.
哦 Shephard先生
Oh, Mr. Shephard.
你好 对 是我叫的
Hello. Yes, that was me.
呃 不好意思 我本该在出口处等你
Uh, sorry, I meant to meet you at the gate.
好吧 嗯 我在这儿了 所以...
Well, um, I'm here now, so...
是这样 Shephard先生 我非常抱歉
Yes. Mr. Shephard, I am deeply sorry,
你在悉尼托运的行李
but there seems to have been a mix-up
好像出了点问题
Involving the, uh... Cargo you checked in sydney.
行李?
Cargo?
是的 先生 是一具棺材
Yes, Sir. A coffin.
我不...
I don't...
我不明白
I don't understand.
我是说 你...你是说棺材不在这儿?
I mean, are...are you saying that it's not here?
事实上棺材根本没被放上飞机
It appears it was never put on the plane.
葬礼还有两小时就开始了 要什么时候才能到?
The funeral is in two hours. When is it getting here?
Shephard先生 我们实在很抱歉
Mr. Shephard, I can't tell you how deeply sorry we are.
但我们也不知道什么时候能到...
But we don't know when it will arrive...
因为我们也不确定它在哪儿
Because we're not exactly sure where it is.
好高的墙啊
That's a big wall.
我们要怎么抬着他翻过去?
How are we gonna get him over the top?
我们不翻 我们从这儿走
We're not. We're bringing him in through here.
谁还带了本书进窑洞?
Who brings a book into a cave?
他又怎么会少了只手臂?
And why is his arm missing?
是黑烟袭击他的时候断掉的
It was ripped off when he was attacked by the black smoke.
好吧... 这事会变的很可怕的
Well... This is gonna be awesome.
注意脚下
Now watch your step.
好的
Yeah.
好了
Okay.
Kate人呢?
Where's Kate?
她刚刚还在那儿
She's right over there.
Kate啊?
Kate?
Kate啊!
Kate!
听得到我吗?!
Can you hear me?!
Kate啊!
Kate!
Jack! 我们不能丢下 Say...
Jack! We can't leave Say...
嘿! 让...
Hey! Let...
Hurley! Jin啊!
Hurley! Jin!
Hurley啊!
Hurley!
你没事吧?
You okay?
- 没事 - 你呢? - 我也没事
- Yeah. - You? - Yeah.
看来我们找到寺庙了
Guess we found the temple.
- 还有什么要补充的吗? - 就是个杀人犯
- Anything to declare? - Just a murderer.
好的
Okay.
我想上厕所
I need to go to the bathroom.
- 憋着 - 憋不住了
- Hold it. - I can't hold it.
当然憋得住 大姐 我相信你可以
Sure you can, kiddo. I believe in you.
Edward啊...
Edward...
求你了
Please.
好吧 过来
All right. Come on.
有人在吗?
Anybody in here?
女厕所里有人吗?
Is anybody in the ladies' room?
别动
Don't move.
可以了
Okay.
给你两分钟时间
You got two minutes.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了没?
You done?
还没
Not yet.
好了 时间到了! 出来吧
All right, time's up! Get out of there.
- 等一下 - 不行 给我马上开门
- One minute. - No, open this door right now.
- 我还没上完 - 你上完了 快开门
- I'm not finished. - Yes, you are. Open it.
Austen 我发誓
Austen, I swear to god,
你要是再不开门 我就进去... 哦!
you don't open this door, I'm coming in there... oh!
虽然我以前也看过 可这次有点... 哦 天啊
Although I've seen it before, it was something... Oh, my god.
我 呃 他... 他刚刚走进来袭击了我
I, uh, he... he just walked in here and attacked me.
我推了他一把 我... 我只是... 我得离开这儿
I pushed him. I... I just... I need to get out of here.
警官 快点来 快来
Officer, come quick. Come quick.
等下 别关门!
Wait, hold the door!
欢迎
Welcome aboard.
我们坐了同班航班 悉尼
We were on the same flight. Sydney.
那又如何?
How about that?
Ganson Calhoun 你们的位置?
Ganson, Calhoun, what's your 20?
呃 我们在南边的电梯里 正要下去
Uh, we're on the south elevator, headed to ground.
快点给我去国际行李区
Get your asses to international baggage claim.
- 我们有第341号麻烦了 - 好的 我们马上到
- We got a 341. - Yeah. We're on our way.
听起来很严重啊
Sounds serious.
什么是第341号麻烦?
What's a 341?
- 这是机密 先生 - 好吧 如果是机密的话
- That's confidential, sir. - Well, if it's confidential,
那我究竟要怎么知道自己有没有看到呢?
How the hell am I supposed to know if I see one?
呃 抱歉
Uh, sorry.
不好意思 女士优先
Excuse me. Ladies first.
谢谢
Thanks.
小心啊
Take care.
我觉得这样就行了 老板
I think that'll do it, boss.
别叫我"老板"了
Stop calling me "boss."
你不再是我的副手了
You ain't my deputy anymore.
你说的对
You got it.
你渴了吗? 我在车上看到有一些啤酒
Are you thirsty? I think I saw some beers in the van.
建筑工人们把他们藏在轮舱里
Construction guys hid 'em in the wheel well.
- 她想告诉我什么 Miles? - 什么?
- What's she want to tell me, miles? - Excuse me?
Juliet啊
Juliet.
她说她想告诉我一些事情 然后就死掉了
She said she wanted to tell me something, and then she died.
是什么事情 Miles?
What was it, Miles?
这就是你要求我和你一起呆在这里的原因吗?
That's why you asked me to stay here with you?
你是我们之中唯一一个能和死人说话的人
You're the only one around that talks to dead people.
J...Jim 我们不能这么做
J...Jim, that's not how it works.
她想告诉我什么 Miles?
What did she wanna tell me, Miles?
- 那... 那不重要 - 它很重要
- It... it doesn't matter. - It does matter.
- 它对我们不会有帮助 - 就这样做吧 就...就去问她...
- It's not gonna help. - Just do it. Just...just ask her...
她已经死了 James
She's gone, James.
我知道她死了 我知道
I know she's gone. I know.
马上告诉我
Now tell me.
好的
Okay.
好
All right.
怎么了?
What?
它起作用了
It worked.
她想告诉我什么?
What did she want to tell me?
这就是她想告诉你的事情
That's what she wanted to tell you.
"它起作用了 "
"It worked."
什么起作用了?
What worked?
就在这里停下
Stop right here.
你们是谁?
Who are you?
我知道他们是谁
I know who they are.
他们在第一架飞机上...
They were on the first plane...
Eanic 815 和我一起的
Eanic 815, along with me.
你确定?
You sure?
杀了他们
Shoot 'em.
哇! 不要 嗨! 不! 不! 不! 不! Jacob要我们来的! Jacob要我们来的!
Whoa! No, hey! No! No! No! No! Jacob sent us! Jacob sent us!
呃 什么... 你刚才说什么?
Uh, what did... what did you just say?
我说Jacob把我们送来的
I said jacob sent us.
他说你会帮助我们的
He said you would help our friend.
他要你拿出证据
He wants you to prove it.
不 他给了我那个吉他盒子
No. He gave me that guitar case!
你看过里面的东西了吗?
Did you look inside it?
也许吧
Maybe.
伙计!
Dude!
你们都叫什么?
What are your names?
我叫Hugo
Hugo.
嗯Hugo reyes
Hugo reyes.
告诉他
Tell him.
我叫Jin-soo Kwon
Jin-soo Kwon.
我是Kate Austen
Kate Austen.
我Jack Shephard
Jack Shephard.
他叫什么?
What about him?
我Sayid Jarrah
Sayid Jarrah.
把他抬起来 送到泉水那里
Pick him up. Get him to the spring.
嘿! 打扰一下
Hey! Excuse me.
我带着那个盒子
I carried that case
漂洋过海 就像 经历了这么长时间
across the ocean and, like, through time,
所以我想知道那张纸上写了什么
so I wanna know what that paper says.
那张纸上说如果你的朋友死了
That paper said that if your friend there dies...
我们都会卷入很多的麻烦之中
we're all in a lot of trouble.
你是从事什么行业的 先生?
And what business are you in, sir?
不会说英语
No english.
准备好你们的护照给海关检阅...
Be prepared to show your passport to customs...
这封信说这个手表是一个生意上的礼品
This letter says the watch is a business gift.
但是你能告诉我是什么生意吗?
But can you tell me what business you're in?
东西都得按次序放好
Everything should be in order.
我们可以走了吗?
May we please continue on our way?
我正赶着要参加一个会议
I have an appointment to get to
退后 先生
Step back, sir.
你用这个做什么?
What are you doing with this?
任何超过10000美元的东西都要登记
Anything over 10,000 has to be declared.
你... 没有... 登记这些
You... didn't... declare this.
为什么... 你为什么会有那些钱?
Why... why do you have all that money?
我会处理的
I will handle this.
先生 你得和我走一趟了
Sir, you're gonna have to come with me.
- 我没有时间 - 我们得谈谈...
- I don't have time for this - Let's go have a talk...
请走这里
This way.
Anee 把她带到等待区
Anne, taer to the waiting area.
Paik小姐?
Ms. Paik?
你懂一点英语吗?
Do you understand any english?
如果你懂的话
Because if you do,
如果这仅仅是一个误会
if this is just a misunderstanding,
你现在就得把它说清楚
you should speak up now.
你能听懂吗?
Do you understand me?
听不懂... 英语
No... English.
水不够清澈
The water isn't clear.
怎么回事?
What happened?
他在干嘛?
What is he doing?
不知道
I don't know.
谁把他弄成这样的?
Who did this to him?
是我的错 我... 没向他开枪 可这是我的错
It's my fault. I... I didn't shoot him, but it's my fault.
如果我们这样做的话 风险很大
If we do this, there are risks.
你明白吗?
You understand?
做你们该做的事吧
Do what you have to do.
把他的衣服脱掉 把他拉进水里
Take off the coveralls, put him in.
他们在做什么?
What are they doing?
- 昏迷的人能屏住呼吸吗? - 不能
- Can unconscious people hold their breath? - No.
他醒了 让他上来吧
He's awake. Let him up.
他们还等什么呢?
What are they waiting for?
够了!
That's enough!
我说让他上来!
I said let him up!
你是在帮倒忙! 快淹死他了!
You're not saving him! You're drowning him!
你朋友死了
Your friend is dead.
Jack啊
Jack.
Jack 停手吧
Jack, stop what you're doing.
Jack 他已经死了
Jack, he's dead.
人死不能复生 停手吧!
He's not coming back. Stop it!
乘坐从阿根廷出发的
Passengers arriving
2230航班抵达的乘客
on Flight 2230 from Argentina,
请于3号传送带提取行李
claim your baggage on carousel 3.
乘坐始发站为巴西圣保罗的
Attention all passengers
3226航班抵达的乘客 请注意
arriving on Flight 3226 from Sao Paulo, Brazil,
请去5号传送带领取行李
please proceed to baggage claim 5.
由基多(厄瓜多尔首都)出发的150号航班已抵达...
Announcing the arrival of Flight 150 from Quito...
请乘客们于85号门登陆
All passengers will disembark from door 85.
欢迎抵达洛杉矶国际机场
Welcome to Los Angeles International Airport.
请勿吸烟 谢谢合作
This is a nonsmoking facility. Thank you.
等等 等等 你不是吧 女士 请排队
Whoa, whoa, whoa. I don't think so, lady. The line.
那么多人等着呢!
There's a line!
抱歉
Sorry.
我们Outback收入如何?
Where are we on the Outback grosses?
Laura在产权登记方面有消息了吗?
Did Laura get a response on the title registration thing?
早该明确下来的
Well, it should've cleared.
Outback只是个名字
Outback's just a name.
他们说自己拥有整个Outback?
What are they saying, they own the entire Outback?
真是扯淡
That's just stupid.
把他们搞定 好吗?
Have'em cover it, okay?
她就要出海关了
She's gonna be coming out of customs,
所以我希望你们走另一个门
so I want you guys to take the other door.
我还没拿到图斯丁库存报告
Oh, I didn't get the, uh, Tustin inventory report yet.
快行动吧
Get on it.
嘿!
Hey!
嘿! 看点路!
Hey! Watch it!
开车! 快开车!
Go! Go now!
女士 已经有人搭我车了
Lady, I already have a customer.
我说快开车
I said go.
嘿 你在干吗?
Hey, what are you doing?
现在开车!
Go now!
嘿! 嘿! 停车!
Hey! Hey! Stop the cab!
我想你们可能需要补充点能量
Thought you might like a little something to eat or drink.
Zack Emma 把剩下的人带过来
Zack, Emma, then take the rest to the people over there.
谢谢
Thank you.
把他们带来
Just drop 'em in here.
嘿 发生什么了?
Hey. What happened?
他们在丛林里抓住我们了
They jumped us in the jungle.
他在他们用岩石砸他前
He took four of them out
解救了他们其中四人
before one of them hit him with a damn rock.
你 跟我来
You. Come with me.
跟你去哪儿?
Come with you where?
他想知道Jacob告诉你什么了
He wants to know what Jacob told you.
他叫我来这里
He told me to come here,
说你们能救Sayid
said you guys would save Sayid.
他已经救不活了
He was beyond saving.
等一下
Wait a sec.
你没有翻译我对他说的话
You're not translating anything I say to him,
也就是说 你完全听懂了 老兄
which means you totally understand me, dude.
我不喜欢说英语
I don't like the way English tastes on my tongue.
- Jacob什么时候来这里? - 你什么意思?
- When's Jacob getting here? - What do you mean?
他要回到寺庙吗?
Is he coming to the temple?
我不这样认为 伙计
I really don't think that's gonna happen, man.
为什么不?
Why not?
你知道... 因为他死了
You know... because he's dead.
什么?
What?
你们不知道?
You guys didn't know?
各就各位!
Everyone to your posts!
上城墙! 准备好灰!
On the walls! Prepare the ash!
北面去十个人!
Ten men to the north side!
发警报!
Send the warning!
点上!
Light it!
我们不是要待在这里吧?
Guess we're not getting out of here, huh?
这不是要困住你们 是防止他进来
This isn't to keep you in. It's to keep him out.
"他"是谁?
"Him" who?
你是什么东西?
What are you?
我不是东西 Ben 我是人
I'm not a "what," Ben. I'm a "who."
你就是那个怪物
You're the monster.
别纠缠于名字了
Let's not resort to name-calling.
你利用我
You used me.
你自己杀不了他
You couldn't kill him yourself,
所以骗我来做
so you made me do it.
我没有骗你做任何事
I didn't make you do anything.
你应该知道...
You should know...
当你杀他的时候 他很困惑
he was very confused when you killed him.
我难以相信Jacob会感到困惑
I seriously doubt that Jacob was ever confused.
我不是说Jacob
I'm not talking about Jacob.
我是说John Locke
I'm talking about John Locke.
你想知道他那时在想什么吗 当你...
Do you wanna know what he was thinking while you...
残忍地勒死他的时候 Benjamin?
choked the life out of him, Benjamin?
他临死前头脑中想的是什么?
What the last thought that ran through his head was?
"我不明白"
"I don't understand."
这是否是你听过的最可怜的事情?
Isn't that just the saddest thing you ever heard?
不过 从某方面看 这也讲得过去
But it's fitting in a way.
因为John第一次踏上这小岛的时候
Because when John first came to the island,
他是一个内心极度悲伤的人
he was a very sad man.
一位受害者
A victim
在得知自己力有不及时 伤心欲绝...
shouting at the world for being told what he couldn't do...
即使这是事实
even though they were right.
他软弱
He was weak
可悲 内心支零破碎
and pathetic and irreparably broken.
但是尽管如此
But despite all that,
他仍有闪光之处
there was something admirable about him.
他是众人中 唯一一个不愿离开小岛的人
He was the only one of them who didn't want to leave.
唯一一个意识到
The only one who realized
他已抛弃的岛外生活是
how pitiful the life he'd left behind
多么地可悲
actually was.
嗯
Hmm.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
这个 极具讽刺意味 Ben
Well, that's the great irony here, Ben,
因为...
because...
我想要的 是John Locke唯一不想要的
I want the one thing that John Locke didn't.
我要回家
I want to go home.
再见 兄弟
Goodbye, dude.
你要是想说会儿话
If you ever wanna talk,
我就在旁边
I'm around.
什么?
What?
没什么
Nothing.
嘿
Hey.
我们在哪?
Where are we?
在寺庙里
We're in a temple.
我们再次被The Others抓了
We got caught by The Others again.
是啊
Yeah.
只有这次 他们是在保护我们
Only this time, they're protecting us.
我这样认为
I think.
当然了
Of course they are.
你还好吗?
You all right?
十分抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你知道你在舱门那里说了什么吗?
You know what you said back at the hatch?
他只是想帮助我们
He's just trying to help us.
我不会杀死Jack
I am not gonna kill Jack.
他理应坐在这块岩石上自我谴责
He deserves to suffer on this rock
和我们其余的人一样
just like the rest of us.
是啊
Yeah.
我知道 而且... 你以为我能预知这事的发生吗?
I know, and... you think I knew this was gonna happen?
我这么快计划好 就是因为想要结束它
I scheduled it so soon because want to get it over with.
所有乘客请注意...
Attention all passengers...
我不知道 妈妈
I don't know, Mom.
他没在这里 所以我不知道让你跟他们如何解释
He's not here, so I can't tell you what to tell them,
只能告诉你 我们没有他办不了事情
other than we can't have the service without him.
嗯
Yeah.
如果有新消息 我会打电话给你的
I will call you if I hear anything.
你掉了什么?
What did you lose?
你说什么?
Excuse me?
哦 他们弄丢了我一个包 你呢?
Oh, they lost one of my bags. What about you?
要是我告诉你 你肯定不会信
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
试试呗
Try me.
他们弄丢了我爸爸
They lost my father.
什么?
I'm sorry?
他几天前在澳大利亚过世
He died in Australia a couple days ago,
然后 呃 我坐飞机来接他的遗体
and, um, I flew down to get him.
节哀顺变
My condolences.
哎
Yo.
棺材本应在悉尼上机
The coffin was supposed to go on the plane in Sydney,
然而却没有
but it didn't.
显然 他被落在了运输途中
Apparently, he's somewhere in transit,
他们敷衍说
which is their way of saying
他们不知道他究竟在哪里
they have no idea where the hell he is.
呃 他们怎么会知道呢?
Well, how could they know?
是他们核准棺材登机的
They're the ones that checked him in.
我是说 他们肯定有什么追踪系统
I mean, they've gotta have some kind of tracking system.
不 我不是在说棺材
No, I'm not talking about the coffin.
我是说 他们怎么知道他在哪里?
I mean, how could they know where he is?
他们没弄丢你爸爸 他们只是弄丢了他的遗体
They didn't lose your father. They just lost his body.
不管怎样 你比我惨
Either way, your story beats the hell out of mine.
我包里不过是一捆刀
All that was in my suitcase was a bunch of knives.
谢谢
Thanks.
你是推销员?
You some kind of salesman?
嗯 差不多
Yeah, somethin' like that.
呃 很高兴和你聊天 我... 我希望你能找到那具棺材
Well, it's nice talking to you. I... I hope you find that coffin.
我希望你能找到你的刀
I hope you find your knives.
嗯 谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
介意我问下 你发生了什么事么?
Mind if I ask what happened to you?
抱歉 之所以有这一问 是因为我是个脊椎外科医生
I'm sorry. I'm only asking because I'm a spinal surgeon.
我... 我不是想...
I... I didn't mean to...
哦 不 别介意 呃...
Oh, no, don't worry about it. Uh...
呃 手术对我没用
Uh, surgery isn't gonna do anythg to help me.
呃 我这情况回天乏术
Uh, my condition is irreversible.
万事皆有转机
Nothing's irreversible.
呃...
Um...
如果你还想咨询一下的话... 就 呃 给我打个电话
If you ever want a consult... just, uh, give me a call.
这是我家里的电话
It's on the house.
嗯 谢谢
Well, thanks.
你叫Jack Shephard
Jack Shephard.
我叫John John Locke
I'm John. John Locke.
- 很高兴认识你 John - 彼此 彼此
- It's nice to meet you, John. - Nice to meet you, too.
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thanks. - You're welcome.
那到底是什么?
What the hell is that?
别开枪! 别杀他!
Don't shoot him! Don't shoot him!
明明该眼见为实
I'm seein' it,
但我却不敢置信
but I'm still not believin' it.
你好 Richard
Hello, Richard.
很高兴看见你摆脱了那些锁链
It's good to see you out of those chains.
是你?
You?
是我
Me.
我对你们每一个人... 都很失望
I am very disappointed... in all of you.
你是Shephard?
You're Shephard?
- 嗯 - 我们需要和你单独谈谈
- Yeah. - We need to speak to you privately.
如果你有话要跟我说 直说就是
If you've got something to say to me, then say it.
否则 就别烦我
Otherwise, just leave me alone.
我想你还没搞明白状况
I don't think you're understanding me here.
我是礼貌相邀
I'm asking politely.
要么你起来 然后乖乖跟我们走
You either get up and come with us on your own,
要么我就把你拖出去
or I'll have you dragged out.
因为我们得好好谈谈
Because we are going to have this conversation,
- 但不在这里谈 - 这样行了吧?
- and it's not going to be here. - Is that right?
Jack啊!
Jack!
哦 老天啊
Oh, my God.
发生了什么事...
What happen...